Guide to the Daniel C. (Daniel Cowan) Jackling Papers, 1911-1956
Department of Special Collections
- LEDGERS AND JOURNALS NOT BOXED
  - Index to D. C. Jackling personal and business files (Volume 99)
    (Numbered files in this collection correspond to numbers in this index volume, thus the volume can be used as a guide. Not all the files index were received and indications are that while Mr. Jackling was alive the files were weeded).
  - D. C. Jackling Cash journals, 1918-1929, 1941-Nov., 1953. (Volume 100-103)
  - D. C. Jackling trust account with Hayden Stone and Company, 1929-1956. (Volume 104)
  - Account book of the International Exploration Corporation, 1929. (Volume 105)
  - Woodside farm cash receipts and disbursements, 1930-56. (Volume 106)
  - History of Bingham [collected and compiled by D. C. Jackling] with early calculations as to feasibility. (Volume 107)